Cross my heart, hope to die Through my lover, I'd never lie
Said be true, I swear I'll try In the end, it's him and I
He's got his head, I'm on my mind We got that love, the crazy kind
I am his, and he is mine In the end, it's him and I
My 65 speeding up the PCH, a hell of a ride They don't wanna see us make it, they just wanna divide
2017, Bonnie and Clyde Wouldn't see the point of living on if one of us died
Got that kind of style, everybody try to rip off YSL dress under when she take the mink off
Silk on her body, pull it down and watch it slip off
Ever catch me cheating, she would try to cut my
Crazy, but I love her, I could never run from her
Hitting no rubber, never would, no one touch her
Swear we'd drive each other mad, she'd be so stubborn
But what the f*** is love with no pain, no suffer
Incense, the s***, it gets dense
She knows when I'm out, I feel like she could just sense
If I had a million dollars, I was down to ten cents
She'd be down for whatever, never gotta convince
I love you, I hope to die Through my lover, I'd never lie
Said be true, I swear I'll try In the end, it's him and I
He's got his head, I'm on my mind We got that love, the crazy kind
I am his and he is mine In the end, it's him and I
In the end, it's him and I
It's her and I, mobbin' to the end of time
Only one who gets me, I'm a crazy f*** Gemini
Remember this for when I die
Everybody dressin' all black, suits in a tie
My funeral be lit if I ever go down or get caught
Or they identify, my b***h was the most solid
Nothing to solidify, she would never cheat
You never see her with a different guy
Ever tell you different, then it's a lie
See that's my down b***h, see that's my soldier
She keep that dang dang, if anyone goes there
We're calm and collected, she keeps her composure
And she gon' ride for me, until this thing over
We do drugs together, we tell claps together
And we both go crazy, if we was to sever
You know, we keep mobbin', it's just me and my b***h
The world, we just gon' keep getting rich, you know
Cross my heart, hope to die
Through my lover, I'd never lie
Said be true, I swear I'll try
In the end, it's him and I
He's got his head, I'm on my mind
We got that love, the crazy kind
I am his and he is mine
In the end, it's him and I
Him and I
Cross my heart, hope to die
To you, I'd never lie
For you, I'd take a life
It's him and I, and I swear
To the end, I'ma ride with you
Mobbin', get money, get high with you
Cross my heart, hope to die
This is our ride or die
You can confide in me, there's none to hide
And I swear
Stay solid, never lie to you
Swear most likely, I'ma die with you
Cross my heart, hope to die
Through my lover, I'd never lie
Said be true, I swear I'll try
In the end, it's him and I
He's got his head, I'm on my mind
We got that love, the crazy kind
I am his and he is mine
In the end, it's him and I
Him and I